When the list item is clicked, use Android's Toast mechanism to display
the weather forecast string. A Toast is a pop-up that displays a message for
a few seconds before fading out. It's particularly useful for debugging, where
it can be used as a way to indicate status visually without altering the app UI.
We're going to put our list view, set item click listener into forecast fragment
inside of the on create view method. We'll just start typing
listView.setOnItemClickListener and
let the auto complete fill in the rest. Inside of this function,
we're going to add click listener, which we can instantiate in place. So
here's where we can call the code in Android to display the Toast. So, now that
you know where to place the Toast code, take a look at the Toast documentation.
Add a Toast when the list item is clicked that contains the weather information.
Hint. You can get the forecast by getting an item from the forecast adapter,
at the position given by the on item click listener.